export const questionsArr = {
  set_1: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "Who is the president of the USA?",
      answers: ["Biden", "Bush", "Clinton", "Obama"],
      correctAnswer: "Biden",
      worth: 100,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question:
        "Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?",
      answers: ["Pocahontas", "Sleeping Beauty", "Cindarella", "Elsa"],
      correctAnswer: "Cindarella",
      worth: 200,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question:
        " What name is given to the revolving belt machinery in an airport that delivers checked luggage from the plane to baggage reclaim?",
      answers: ["Hangar", "Terminal", "Concourse", "Carousel"],
      correctAnswer: "Carousel",
      worth: 300,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question:
        "Which of these brands was chiefly associated with the manufacture of household locks?",
      answers: ["Phillips", "Flymo", "Chubb", "Ronseal"],
      correctAnswer: "Chubb",
      worth: 500,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question:
        "The hammer and sickle is one of the most recognisable symbols of which political ideology?",
      answers: ["Republicanism", "Communism", "Conservatism", "Liberalism"],
      correctAnswer: "Communism",
      worth: 1000,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question:
        "2,000 - Which toys have been marketed with the phrase “robots in disguise”?",
      answers: [
        "Bratz Dolls",
        "Sylvanian Families",
        "Hatchimals",
        "Transformers",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Transformers",
      worth: 2000,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "What does the word loquacious mean?",
      answers: ["Angry", "Chatty", "Beautiful", "Shy"],
      correctAnswer: "Chatty",
      worth: 4000,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question:
        " Obstetrics is a branch of medicine particularly concerned with what?",
      answers: ["Childbirth", "Broken bones", "Heart conditions", "Old age"],
      correctAnswer: "Childbirth",
      worth: 8000,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question:
        "In Doctor Who, what was the signature look of the fourth Doctor, as portrayed by Tom Baker?",
      answers: [
        "Bow-tie, braces and tweed jacket",
        "Wide-brimmed hat and extra long scarf",
        "Pinstripe suit and trainers",
        "Cape, velvet jacket and frilly shirt",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Wide-brimmed hat and extra long scarf",
      worth: 1600,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question:
        "Which of these religious observances lasts for the shortest period of time during the calendar year?",
      answers: ["Ramadan", "Diwali", "Lent", "Hanukkah"],
      correctAnswer: "Diwali",
      worth: 32000,
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question:
        "At the closest point, which island group is only 50 miles south-east of the coast of Florida?",
      answers: [
        "Bahamas",
        "US Virgin Islands",
        "Turks and Caicos Islands",
        "Bermuda",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Bahamas",
      worth: 65000,
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question:
        "Construction of which of these famous landmarks was completed first?",
      answers: [
        "Empire State Building",
        "Royal Albert Hall",
        "Eiffel Tower",
        "Big Ben Clock Tower",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Big Ben Clock Tower",
      worth: 125000,
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: "Which of these cetaceans is classified as a “toothed whale”?",
      answers: ["Gray whale", "Minke whale", "Sperm whale", "Humpback whale"],
      correctAnswer: "Sperm whale",
      worth: 250000,
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question:
        "Who is the only British politician to have held all four “Great Offices of State” at some point during their career?",
      answers: [
        "David Lloyd George",
        "Harold Wilson",
        "James Callaghan",
        "John Major",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "James Callaghan",
      worth: 500000,
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question:
        "In 1718, which pirate died in battle off the coast of what is now North Carolina?",
      answers: [
        "Calico Jack",
        "Blackbeard",
        "Bartholomew Roberts",
        "Captain Kidd",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Blackbeard",
      worth: 1000000,
    },
  ],
};

